paizo.com 2012-05-31

# paizo.com - Paizo / About Paizo / Privacy Policy

##  Paizo Publishing, LLC Website Privacy Policy 

### This document was last updated February 1, 2012

We at Paizo Publishing are committed to protecting your personal information. This policy applies to transactions made and data gathered on the paizo.com website, and does not apply to any other website or offline contact between Paizo Publishing and consumers.

Each time you visit paizo.com or provide us with information, you are accepting the practices as described in the policy at that time.

Please review the Privacy Policy from time to time as we may update it periodically.

**Information We Collect From You**  
To provide you with products and services, we may collect personal information (i.e. name, mailing address, phone number, email address), financial information (i.e. credit card numbers and billing addresses), and demographic information (i.e. zip code, age). Please note that nowhere on this site do we knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**  
We use the information you provide for us to help us deliver the services you have requested, to contact you when necessary in connection with those service requests, and to send you information regarding your order or requested services. Note that you cannot opt out of transactional emails, such as order confirmations or shipment notices. In some cases, it is necessary for us to provide information particular to you to a third party. For example, in the case of the magazines that we previously published, it was necessary for us to provide your name and mailing address to the printer for the production of delivery information, to a service that provided notification regarding the expiration of your subscription, and/or to a delivery company so that you could receive your magazine. Also, in the case of subscriptions to _Dragon_ or _Dungeon_ magazines, pertinent subscription information was also provided to Wizards of the Coast, Inc.

We use the financial information you give us to check your qualifications and to charge you for products and services you order from us. By making a purchase or engaging in other activity on the Site that uses financial information, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service providers and the third parties necessary to process your transactions.

If you participate in Pathfinder Society organized play, your participation in games is recorded and may be disclosed to volunteer Venture Captains. This information is limited to information about your participation and does not include any personal, financial or demographic information.

If you use the private messaging system, messages sent and received are visible to the sender and recipient. Messages may be reviewed by Paizo staff or disclosed to appropriate law enforcement agencies if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to investigate abuse or ensure personal safety.

Customers may "opt in" to register interest with [Goblinworks Games](http://goblinworksgames.com/), publishers of the officially licensed MMO _Pathfinder Online_. Paizo may share those customers' personal and demographic information with Goblinworks.

Paizo occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services. If you do not want to receive these offers, you should uncheck the boxes in the Privacy Settings section of the "[My Account](https://secure.paizo.com/paizo/account)" area under the "Partners" heading.

Paizo may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Paizo or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Paizo and its web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Paizo, its web sites, or the public.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Paizo or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Paizo abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Access and Control of your Personal Information**  
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, Paizo will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

You have the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time in the "[My Account](https://secure.paizo.com/paizo/account)" area of paizo.com or by sending a request to [customer.service@paizo.com](mailto:customer.service@paizo.com). You can:

  * View and edit personal information you have already given us. 
  * Tell us whether you want Paizo to send you marketing information. 
  * Choose whether you want third parties to send you their offers. 
  * Subscribe, or cancel subscriptions, to newsletters about our services and products. 
  * Opt out of the private messaging system.

**Information Other Websites Collect From You**  
If there are links from our site to other websites operated by other parties, please be aware that by clicking on those links you are entering sites where our privacy policy does not apply. We encourage you to review their privacy policies, and remind you that we are not responsible for their actions.

**Changes to this Statement**  
Paizo will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, Paizo will notify you by placing prominent notice on the web site.

**Contact**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, or about your dealings with the Paizo Publishing, LLC website, contact [customer.service@paizo.com](mailto:customer.service@paizo.com).
